>> 演讲者 1: 请解释该加号
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Could you explain the plus
在 eventTargetDataSetIndex 前再次登录吗 ?
sign in front of
eventTargetDataSetIndex again?
>> Brian Holt: 从数据集中返回某些内容时，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: When you get back
something from the data set,
就会是个字符串对吧
it's gonna be a string, right?
就像绳子五
Like a string five.
我需要它是一个数字，而不是一个字符串，对吧 ?
And I need it to be a number,
not a string, right?
所以如果我放了 +string5
So if I put +string5.
我的实际数是 5
I get back the actual number of five.
>> 扬声器 1: 好，当然，它是一个整数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Okay, so
of course, it's an integer.
>> Brian Holt: 数字，是的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: A number, yeah.
所以你也可以只说 parseInt("5"，10)
So you could have also
just said parseInt("5",10)
这就意味着你要在 10 号的基地里
which just means you want
it to be in base ten.
这也会给你同样的东西
And that would give you
the same thing as well.
但是，加号是远远不够的。
But plus signs is far less work, so.
这里可能有类似的东西，别在这里买东西了。
Very well there might be something
like this, stop buying this here.
那就这样吧
So.
>> 扬声器 3: 然后对该调用添加索引。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And
then adding index to that call.
>> Brian Holt: 是的，你也可以这样做
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, and you could have
done this as well right, for sure and
那么此处没有数据集。
then not had the data set here.
>> Brian Holt: 这样做就像这样，而不是得到
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So then this would have
had worked like this instead of getting
活动。
an event.
>> Brian Holt: 会有这样的索引，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There would have
been an index like this and
那你就只会打指数了
then you would've just been calling index.
>> Brian Holt: 是，此工作。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yes, this works.
那么让我告诉你们为什么人们在历史上没有这样做，
So let me tell you why people have
historically not done this, and
那我就告诉你为什么没有人这样做
then I'll tell you why that's silly
that people haven't done it this way.
>> Brian Holt: 这样做会起作用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this does work.
人员未使用此操作，因为此调用绑定已使用
People did not used to do this,
because this calling bind used
比你预想的要贵得多
to be very expensive, far more expensive
than you would have ever expected.
它曾经是你在 Chrome中可以做的最慢的事情之一。
It used to be one of the slowest
things you could do in Chrome.
大约两年前， Chrome 固定了这个，使点的绑定更快。
Now about two years ago, Chrome fixed
this and made dot bind much faster.
但为什么这与构造函数不同呢 ?
But why is this different from
doing it in the constructor?
这就不一样了，因为每次我打电话给人，都是有约束力的，对吧 ?
This is different because every time I
call render, this is calling bind, right?
如果真的这么做意味着你放慢了投降的速度
And if that was really so
that means you slow down your renders,
这意味着您将降低整个应用程序的性能。
which means that you're slowing down the
performance of your entire application.
所以人们建立了最好的做法，不要这样做。
So people have established the best
practice of, don't do it this way.
但好消息是他们确定了
But the good news is, they fixed it.
现在的速度要快得多。
It is much faster now.
所以这其实是有效的，但是我们还是要处理旧的浏览器
And so this does actually work okay, but
we still have to deal with old browsers
所以在旧的浏览器中，这还是很缓慢的。
and so in old browsers,
this is still really slow.
所以它运作缓慢而且很缓慢
So it works and it's slow,
it's creating and
每次都破坏功能
destroying functions every single time.
你把这个跑了现在又有钩子了
That you run this,
which hooks do now anyway.
所以我不太确定那是什么大不了的
So I'm not really too sure if
that's a big deal anymore.
但这个问题的真正答案是，点绑定最终会变得昂贵。
But the real answer to that question is
the dot bind ends up being expensive.